<?xml version="1.0"?>
<locations>
    <spot>
        <attraction>White Island</attraction>
        <address>White Beach, Boracay, Aklan</address>
        <details>Boracay's White Beach has been recognized as one of the most beautiful beaches in the world through the years. There's something about its natural beauty – its crystal blue water, its pure white sand, and its magical sunsets.</details>
    </spot>
    <spot>
        <attraction>Boracay Island</attraction>
        <address>Boracay Island, Banwa it Malay, Aklan</address>
        <details>Boracay Island is a very small island in Philippines. But, what it offers is completely opposite to its size. With an infinite number of activities both above water and underwater, the island will amaze you like never before.</details>
    </spot>
    <spot>
        <attraction>Boracay Beach Path</attraction>
        <address>White Beach Path, Malay, Aklan</address>
        <details>White Beach Path runs alongside White Beach, starting from Boat Station 1 and terminating by Lorenzo South. Most of the island's business' are concentrated on this strip.</details>
    </spot>
    <spot>
        <attraction>Bulabog Beach</attraction>
        <address>Bulabog Beach, Banwa it Malay, Aklan</address>
        <details>Bulabog Beach is a beautiful beach located on the eastern side of Boracay Island in the Philippines. It is famous for its vibrant and dynamic atmosphere, particularly among windsurfers and kiteboarders.</details>
    </spot>
    <spot>
        <attraction>Tambisaan Beach</attraction>
        <address>Boracay Tambisaan Jetty Port Rd, Malay, Aklan</address>
        <details>Tambisaan Beach is a hidden gem located on the eastern side of Boracay Island in the Philippines. Tambisaan Beach is another beautiful beach located on the eastern side of Boracay Island in the Philippines. It offers a more tranquil and secluded experience compared to the bustling White Beach.</details>
    </spot>
    <spot>
        <attraction>Puka Shell Beach</attraction>
        <address>Puka Shell Beach, Banwa it Malay, Aklan</address>
        <details>Puka Shell Beach in Boracay is a picturesque stretch of white sand known for its abundance of puka shells and tranquil atmosphere.</details>
    </spot>
    <spot>
        <attraction>Savoy Beach</attraction>
        <address>Savoy Beach, Banwa it Malay, Aklan</address>
        <details>Savoy beach has a nice crystal waters which you can explore, It offers a family-friendly environment with a variety of amenities tailored for travelers, offering the perfect balance of value, comfort, and convenience.</details>
    </spot>
    <spot>
        <attraction>Hagdan Beach</attraction>
        <address>Hagdan Beach, Banwa it Malay, Aklan</address>
        <details>Hagdan Beach is unique from other beaches on the island because of its various-sized rock formations. It is also an appealing attraction for a lot of individuals, particularly those who enjoy swimming, diving, boating, and sea cruise.</details>
    </spot>
    <spot>
        <attraction>Balinghai Beach</attraction>
        <address>Balinghai Beach, Banwa it Malay</address>
        <details>Balinghai Beach in Boracay is a secluded and secluded cove surrounded by cliffs, known for its crystal-clear waters, vibrant coral reefs, and peaceful atmosphere, perfect for those seeking a serene beach getaway.</details>
    </spot>
    <spot>
        <attraction>Diniwid Beach</attraction>
        <address>Diniwid Beach, Banwa it Malay, Aklan</address>
        <details>Diniwid Beach in Boracay is a picturesque and tranquil strip of white sand nestled between lush cliffs, offering a serene escape from the bustling crowds of the island's main beach.</details>
    </spot>
</locations>
